<setup>
	<block title="HPfeeds Configuration">
		<text>
            This appplication is designed to create clustered parallel coordinates graphs with data received from HPfeeds channels. HPfeeds is a centralized transport protocol for security events from the Honeynet Project sensor network. In order to retreive data from the HPfeeds system, you need to introduce all the following configuration parameters.
         </text>
	</block>
        <block title="HPfeeds Broker Settings" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<text>
			You need to enter the hostname (or IP address) and port for the HPfeeds broker you want to use.
		</text>
		<input field="broker_host">
			<label>Hostname</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
        <block title="" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<input field="broker_port">
			<label>Port</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
        <block title="Your HPfeeds Authkey (required for channel subscription)" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<text>
			You need to enter your authkey information before trying to subscribe to an HPfeeds channel.
                        Warning: Your authkey must have "subscribe" permission for all the channels you'll want to index in Splunk.
                        
                        If you don't have an authkey yet. You must create one on the broker you'll want to use.
		</text>
		<input field="authkey_id">
			<label>Authkey ID</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
	<block title="" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<input field="authkey_secret">
			<label>Authkey Secret</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
        <block title="HPfeeds Channel Subscriptions" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<text>
			Enter the channels you want to subscribe to.
                        This parameter must be a comma-separated list of channel names.
                        e.g: channel1,channel2,channel3,...
                        
                        WARNING: for each HPfeeds channel subscribed a new Splunk index is created. Thus, when
                        subscribing for the first time to a new channel, you MUST restart Splunk to activate the
                        newly created index.
		</text>
		<input field="channel_list">
			<label>Channel List</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
        <block title="Log files Path" endpoint="admin/hpfeeds/" entity="hpfeeds_settings">
		<text>
			Enter the path for log files.
                        All the data received for a given HPfeeds channel is stored in a dedicated file.
                        This file is then monitored by Splunk.
                        Warning: the path must exist and must be writable.
                        
		</text>
		<input field="logfilepath">
			<label>Log Files Path</label>
			<type>text</type>
		</input>
	</block>
        <block title="Warning">
		<text>Please be patient and wait for this form to complete before navigating away from this page.
                
                </text>
	</block>
</setup>
